eastwood.com 2012-06-23

# Customer Service - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

The Eastwood Company recognizes that you value the privacy of your personal information and how it is utilized. We value your trust and continued patronage and will utilize the information we collect in a manner that will benefit your overall shopping experience.

TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") is data about you that is personally identifiable: your name, email address, credit card number or any other information that is not otherwise publicly available. Eastwood only collects PII when you supply it to us by placing an order, entering a contest, or requesting e-mail announcements. That information is maintained by Eastwood so that you do not have to enter it each time you visit our to place an order.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information ("NPII") is collected by Eastwood for the purpose of online retargeting. NPII data collected by Eastwood for advertising purposes is completely anonymous, and only includes information such as the IP address, date and time of visit, domain type, and activity on our website. None of this information, individually or grouped together, can be traced back to a specific individual.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT AUTOMATICALLY

Our web server will automatically recognize and store the following NPII: browser type and version, IP address, operating system, URL, pages visited, time spent on each page. This information is primarily used to improve our web site and enhance your shopping experience. For example, an infrequently visited page may be eliminated. In addition, we will utilize the information for product offerings or to improve navigation throughout the site.

COOKIES

A cookie is a string of text used to allow for authentication, session tracking, and storing site preferences.

You do not need to accept or use cookies to shop at eastwood.com.

The cookies we use assist us in determining Web site traffic patterns. These cookies help us better understand how visitors navigate through and use eastwood.com, enabling us to measure the site's ease of use and effectiveness. This information assists us in our efforts to refine our site, as well as efforts to improve and customize the shopping experience for individual visitors like you.

The cookies we employ contain absolutely no PII. If you do not want to receive cookies, you can set your browser to accept no cookies, or tell it to erase all cookies at the end of a session.

However, if you choose to disable cookies, you may not be able to use features such as My Account or Wish Lists.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

HOW WE UTILIZE COOKIES AND NPII

The cookies we employ allow us to use third-party vendors to more effectively distribute our ads and to improve the quality and relevance of advertising you see. When you visit other sites, third-party vendors are able to identify the Eastwood cookie and provide you with pertinent advertising based on your browsing history. None of the information used in this remarketing process is personally-identifiable information (PII).

INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE

Eastwood stores information you provide when placing an order, entering a promotional event or requesting e-mail announcements. Name, address and phone number are required when you place an order. Email addresses are utilized to confirm orders have been placed or shipped and provide customers -with new product announcements and special savings.

SECURITY OF INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE

We work to protect the security of the information you provide during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION PROVIDED

The Eastwood Company recognizes that privacy of personal information is of the utmost importance. Therefore, information will only be shared with approved partners. The partner approval process involves an analysis of the ethical standards of the prospective partner, product/service quality, reputation, how our customers will be approached and treated, the likelihood of partner's product/service appealing to Eastwood customers and other factors as well.

AGENTS

Occasionally, we will employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf. These companies do have access to personal information while fulfilling their obligations, but do not have the authority to utilize any information.

CONSENT

By accessing The Eastwood Company web site to gather information or place product orders, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information.

QUESTIONS OR SUGGESTIONS?

If you have questions or suggestions, send an email to webmaster@eastwood.com.

**CLICK HERE TO VIEW OUR TERMS& CONDITIONS**

[  
ABOUT SSL CERTIFICATES](http://www.thawte.com/digital-certificates/)
